// questiondb = [
//   {
//     question:"what0",
//     answers:[["0",0],["1",1],["2",2]],
//     correctAnswer: 0
//   },
//   {
//     question:"why2",
//     answers:[["0",0],["1",1],["2",2],["3",3],["4",4]],
//     correctAnswer: 2
//   },
//   {
//     question:"who3",
//     answers:[["0",0],["1",1],["2",2],["3",3]],
//     correctAnswer: 3
//   },
//   {
//     question:"where1",
//     answers:[["0",0],["1",1],["2",2],["3",3]],
//     correctAnswer: 1
//   },
//   {
//     question:"when2",
//     answers:[["0",0],["1",1],["2",2],["3",3]],
//     correctAnswer: 2
//   }
// ];

questiondb = [
  {
    question:"How many questions are in this trivia game?",
    answers:[["12",0],["5",1],["46",2]],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question:"How much time do you get for each question?",
    answers:[["20",0],["Daylight Savings Time isn't real",1],["Temporal measurement is an arbitrary concept",0],["Time is an illusory social construct",3],["30",4]],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    question:"I can't think of trivia questions",
    answers:[["I agree",1],["I agree",1],["I agree",1],["I disagree",0]],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    question:"Is this a question",
    answers:[["no",0],["yes",1],["?",2],[".",3]],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    question:"Why are the questions in this game weird?",
    answers:[["to test my power",1],["to test my power",1],["to test my power",1],["to test my power",1]],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
];
